A Guide to the Melvin E. Steadman collection, 1698-1927
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Local records, 1755-1927., Extent: 10 boxes. (Box 1-10)
  - Loudoun County Deed Book K, 1773-1775. (Box 5, Folder 29, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between Robert Smith and Simon Hancock (1775).
    Deed between Thomas Aubrey and Richard Aubrey (1775).
    Deed between Cornelius Bodine and Leven Powell (1775).
    Deed between Elias John and Abraham Dawson (1775).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book K#2, 1805. (Box 5, Folder 30, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deeds between Lewis Ellzey and William Ellzey.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book K#3, 1825. (Box 5, Folder 31, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between Christopher Frye and John Watt.
    Deed between George Head and John Shaw to Simon Small.
    Deed between George Head and Lydia Head.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book L, 1773-1799. (Box 5, Folder 32, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between Craven Peyton and Charles West (1775), 2 copies.
    Deposition of Dempsey Carroll (1775).
    Deed between Robert Johnson and Robert Bland (1775), 2 copies.
    Deed between John Pursel and Thomas Pursel (1775).
    Deed between Daniel McIntosh and Israel Thompson (1775).
    Deed between Hezekiah Guy and Thomas Lewis (1775).
    Deed between Philip Grymes and Joseph Cross (1776).
    Deed between William Mitchell and John Orr (1776).
    Deed between Jesse Oxley and Mahlon Taylor (1777), 2 copies.
    Power of attorney of Charles West (1776).
    Deed between Jacob Ramey and Charles Ramey (1777).
    Deed between John Corrie and Spencer Clark (1777), 2 copies.
    Power of attorney of Leven Powell (1777).
    Deed between Robert Armistead and Charles Smith (1798).
    Deed between Mary Armistead and Frances Hill Westwood (1799).
    Deed between Mary Armistead to Robert Armistead (1799).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book L#2, 1803-1831. (Box 5, Folder 33, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between A.T. Mason, Westwood Mason, and William Mason (1803).
    Deed between Joshua Comstock and Leesburg Turnpike Company (1829).
    Deed between James Roberdeau and James Coleman (1831).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book M, 1769-1779. (Box 6, Folder 1, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between William Ellzey and John Markley (1769).
    Deed between Thomas Brown and William Finch (1776).
    Deed between John Thornton and James Whaley (1777).
    Deed between Elijah Major and John Walker (1778), 2 copies.
    Deed between William Finch and James Lane (1778).
    Deed between Richard Major and Thomas Oden (1778), 2 copies.
    Deed between William Martin and Robert White (1778).
    Deed between John Miller and Amos Thompson (1778).
    Estate of William Martin (1778).
    Deed between Thompson Mason and Josiah Clapham (1778).
    Deed between Henry McCabe and Joshua Taylor (1778).
    Deed between Arthur Edwards and James Gibbs (1778).
    Estate of Sarah Leggo (1778).
    Deed between Stanley Singleton and John Singleton (1779).
    Deed between William Blincoe and Edward Carter (1779).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book M#2, 1810. (Box 6, Folder 2, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between Thomas Love and Samuel Hughes, 2 copies.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book N, 1779-1781. (Box 6, Folder 3, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between Joseph Moxley and John Piles (1779), 2 copies.
    Deed between John Drane and Andrew Specht (1781).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book O, 1784. (Box 6, Folder 4, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Division of Hugh West estate.
    Deed between Christopher Perfect and Jane McIntyre.
    Deed between Martin Ashby and George Noble.
    Deed between Richard Vallandigham and Bryan Fairfax.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book O#2, 1808-1812. (Box 6, Folder 5, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1230)
    Deed between Lewis Ellzey and David Lovett (1808).
    Deed between Martin Brent and Robert J. Taylor (1811).
    Deed between trustees of the town of Hillsborough and Henry Griffin (1811).
    Deed between Westwood Mason, Samuel Ramey, and John A. Binns (1812).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book P, 1784-1787. (Box 6, Folder 6, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed between George W. Fairfax and John Evans (1784).
    Deed between John Davis and Jacob Davis (1785).
    Deed between Aneau Campbell and Lydia McGrath (1785).
    Deed between Nathaniel Weedon and Thomas Lewis (1786).
    Deed between Thomas Noland and Phillip Noland (1786).
    Deed between Phillip Noland and Otho Luckett and Sarah Noland (1786).
    Deed between James Monteith and Aberneth Rogers (1786).
    Deed between John Crane and Christopher Grump (1786).
    Deed between Phillip Noland and Thomas Luckett (1786).
    Deed between George W. Fairfax and William Osborne (1786).
    Deed between Amos Thomas and William Lane (1787).
    Deed between George W. Fairfax and Andrew Copeland (1787).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book P#2, 1812. (Box 6, Folder 7, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed between Abraham B.T. Mason and Thomson Mason.
    Division of the estate of William Dulin.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book Q, 1787-1788. (Box 6, Folder 8, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed between Charles Thornton and Nathaniel Moss (1787).
    Deed between Charles Stewart and George Lewis (1787).
    Deed between Leonard Wheeler and Charles Shepherd (1787).
    Power of attorney of Jacob Yandas (1787).
    Power of attorney of Hugh Douglass (1787).
    Power of attorney of George Boswell (1787).
    Bond to George Summers. (1787).
    Power of attorney of George Taylor (1787).
    Deed between Bushrod Washington and Peter Mathew (1787).
    Deed between George W. Fairfax and Joseph Scott (1788).
    Deed between Isaac Hutchinson and Samuel Love (1788).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book Q#2, 1813. (Box 6, Folder 9, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed between Alfred Belt and Westwood Mason.
    Deed between Charles F. Mercer and Aaron Marstellar.
    Deed between William Divines and Henry Jenkins.
    Deed between Ludwell Lee and George Berkley.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book Q#4, 1841. (Box 6, Folder 10, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed and survey between George Lee and John Janney.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book R, 1774-1789. (Box 6, Folder 11, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed between Edward Blackburn and Henry Jenkins (1774).
    Deed between John Bagley and Alexander Binns (1787).
    Deed between William Woollard and Isaac Larrowe (1787).
    Deed between Maryann Boggess, John Alexander, and John Green to Hugh Conn (1788).
    Deed between Simon Hancock and John Butcher (1789).
    Deed between Leven Powell and John McFarland (1789).
    Deed between William Buchannon and John Donaldson (1789).
    Deed between Benjamin Rieger and P. Cowan (1789).
    Deed between Elizabeth Bayley and Joseph Bayley (1789).
    Deed between John Wren and Peter Herbert (1789).
    Bond of George Summers (1789).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book R#3, 1824-1828. (Box 6, Folder 12, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed between Thompson Mason and Farmers and Merchants Bank of Georgetown (1824).
    Deed between Simon Rust and William Ish (1828).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book R#5, 1859. (Box 6, Folder 12a)
    Deed between Francis Van Buren and Richard H. Laskey.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book S, 1790. (Box 6, Folder 13, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed between John Davis and William Beans, 2 copies.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book S#4, 1843. (Box 6, Folder 14, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed between Ariss Buckner and Spencer Buckner.
    Deed between William Snyder and John Janney.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book S#7, 1899. (Box 6, Folder 15, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed between H. F. Buckner and Peter Polend.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book T, 1790-1792. (Box 6, Folder 16, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed between Job Robinson and Robert McCullough (1790).
    Deed between Benjamin Cockerill and Jeremiah Cockerill (1791).
    Deed between William Sears and Simon Triplett (1791).
    Deed between Francis Berryman and Michael Ashford (1791).
    Deed between Jacob Remey and Samuel Love (1791).
    Bond of James Coleman and Josias Clapham (1791).
    Bond of James Currell (1791).
    Deed between Tankerville and Bennett and John Douglass (1792).
    Deed between Leven Powell and Leven Powell and Sons (1792).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book T#2, 1816. (Box 6, Folder 17, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Map and report of the Town of Bloomfield.
    Deed between Margaret Douglass and John T. Mason.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book T#3, 1830. (Box 6, Folder 18, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed between John Binns and Mary Hough.
    Deed between William Mason and Charles J. Cattlett.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book U, 1792-1793. (Box 6, Folder 19, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed between Peter Bayley and Tarpley Bayley (1792).
    Deed between Nathaniel Barker and Charles Lane (1792).
    Deed between Albert Russell and Theodorick Lee (1792).
    Deed between John Wren and Samuel Harriman (1792).
    Deed between Joseph Janney and Mahlon Janney (1792).
    Deed between Peter Romine and James Grady (1792).
    Deed between Robert Scott and James Coleman (1792).
    Deed between Hugh Douglass and Clare Oxley (1792).
    Deed between Dennis Wagoner and Scarlett Berkley (1792).
    Deed between Anthony Thornton and Charley Thruston (1792).
    Deed between Samuel Love and Nelly Love (1792).
    Richard Conner's certificate of importation of slaves (1792).
    Deed between John Schooley and Richard Miller (1792).
    Deed between John Schooley and John Hough (1792).
    Deed between George Carter and Martin Wildman (1792).
    Deed between Samuel Hough and William Stabler (1792).
    Deed between Charles Tankerville and Henry Giese (1793).
    Deed between Charles Tankerville and Christian Beagle (1793).
    Deed between Abraham Lap and Isaac Nickols (1793).
    Deed between John Trebee and George Rine(1793).
    Power of attorney of William Peake (1793).
    Deed between Thomas Oden and John Kimble (1793).
    Deed between Samuel Love, John Gunnell, and M. Harrison (1793).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book U#4, 1845. (Box 6, Folder 20, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed between William Snider and John Janney.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book V, 1793. (Box 6, Folder 21, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed between Gray Douglass and John Wren.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book W#2, 1816. (Box 6, Folder 22, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed between Thomas Huse and Samuel Huse.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book W#4, 1846. (Box 6, Folder 23, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed between William Dvish and William McVeigh.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book X, 1795. (Box 6, Folder 24, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed between Theodorich Lee and David Stuart.
  - Loudoun County Deed Book Y, 1795-1797. (Box 6, Folder 25, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed between Alexander Smith and William Bloxham (1795).
    Deed between Samuel Love and Hugh Stuart on behalf of Sidney Clarke (1796).
    Deed between George Hancock and Elizabeth Hancock (1797).
    Deed between Levy Hole and Joseph Janney (1797).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book Z, 1797-1799. (Box 6, Folder 26, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed between John Lewis and John Lewis Jr. (1797).
    Deed between John Owens and John Dowdell (1798).
    Deed between Daniel Stuart and Charles Lewis (1798).
    Deed between trustees of Centerville and Samuel Love (1798).
    Deed between John Loch and Barton Lucus (1798).
    Deed between Frederic Lambert and Conrad Shaffer (1798).
    Deed between Joseph Carr and Ambrose Fox (1799).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book Unrecorded Deeds Not In Index, 1774-1823. (Box 6, Folder 27, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Deed between Thomas Blincoe and Coward Smith (1774).
    Deed between Joseph Read and Barbara Berkley (1779).
    Deed between Mahlon Taylor and James Saunders (1777.
    Deed between Mahlon Taylor and Samuel Pleasants (1777).
    Deed between Joseph Taylor and Nicholas Byrne (1782).
    Deed between Mason Johnson and Benjamin Edwards (1789).
    Deed between Archibald Reynolds and William Shreve (1790).
    Deed between George Rhine and Thomas Wilkerson (1794).
    Deed between Walter Perry and Edward Talbot (1794).
    Deed between Thomas Oden and William Rose (1795).
    Deed between Samuel Adams and William Field (1795).
    Deed between Daniel Romine and John Scatterday (1796).
    Deed between Winn Winship and James Belch (1797).
    Deed between Leven Powell and William Hodgson (1801).
    Deed between Christopher Roper and Thomas Wilkerson (1801).
    Deed between Robert Wheeler and Patrick Durney (1803).
    Deed between John Bussel and Thomas White (1806).
    Deed between Henry Smith and Mahlon Taylor (1809).
    Deed between John Roberts and Isaac Lacy (1809).
    Deed between Samuel Palmer and Benjamin Palmer (1811).
    Deed between Hamon Pattison and Isaac Walker (1815).
    Deed between William Hook and Elijah James (1817).
    Deed between George Rust and Hamilton Elgin (1818).
    Deed between Abraham Brown and Spencer Lake (1820).
    Deed between Robert Oneal and Abraham Skillman (1828).
  - Loudoun County Deed Book Unrecorded Deeds Grantor A, 1764-1838. (Box 6, Folder 28, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1231)
    Power of attorney of Wilfred Atkinson (1764).
    Deed between Henry Ashton and George Mason (1782).
    Deed between Edward Adams and William Deneale (1784).
    Deed between William Adams and Edward Adams (1789).
    Deed between John Alexander and John Brown (1792).
    Deed between Adam Axline and Isaac Miller (1793).
    Deed between Edward Adams and Jonias Clapham (1794).
    Deed between John Armistead and John Thornton (1798).
    Deed between John B. Armistead and Maurice Moore (1798).
    Deed between John Ashford and John Spencer (1790).
    Deed between Mary Armistead and Armistead Thomson Mason (1803).
    Deed between Elijah Anderson and Samuel Boggess (1810).
    Deed between Thomas Arnett and Benjamin Jackson (1811).
    Deed between Henry Ashbury and William Rose (1812).
    Deed between Mary Alexander and Uriah McKnight (1813).
    Deed between Abraham Anderson and John Ross (1823).
    Deed between Charles B. Alexander and William Binns (1827).
  - Loudoun County Unrecorded Deeds Grantor Ba-Bla, 1772-1846. (Box 7, Folder 1, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1232)
    Deed between Edward Bland and Robert Johnston (1772).
    Deed between John Ballendine and Peter Foreman (1780).
    Deed between William Bayley and Samuel Bayley (1780).
    Deed between Joseph Bayley and Tarpley Bayley (1784).
    Deed between Henry Barband and Thomas Hawkins (1792).
    Deed between Mountjoy Bayley and Taplay Bayley (1792).
    Deed between Nathan Ball and John Binns (1798).
    Deed between William Barricraft and William Mains (1798).
    Deed between Farling Ball and Isaac Ball (1798).
    Deed between Lydia Bentley and John Bentley (1799).
    Deed between Stephen Ball and Isaac Ball (1803).
    Deed between John Baker and William Wenner (c. 1804).
    Deed between Thomas Barr and George and Adam Barr (1804).
    Deed between Joseph Beale and David Lovell (1805).
    Deed between Elizabeth Barton and Joseph Barton etc. (1810).
    Deed between George Barr and Stacy Taylor (1811).
    Deed between Joseph Barton and John Ralph (1812).
    Deed between Solomon Betton and Charles Love (1813).
    Deed between John Beatty and David Little (1813).
    Deed between Thomas Beatty and George Rhodes (1817).
    Deed between William Benton and John Martin, etc. (1821).
    Deed between Charles Binns and Robert Moffett (1821).
    Deed between James Beavers and William Smarr (1823).
    Deed between Thomas Beatty and Peyton Paul (1825).
    Deed between James Biscoe and William Mershon (1830).
    Deed between William Binns and John Binns (1830).
    Deed between Absalom Beans and Fenton Love etc. (1846).
  - Loudoun County Unrecorded Deeds Grantor Bli-Bu, 1774-1825. (Box 7, Folder 2, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1232)
    Deed between John Buckner and William Lane (1774).
    Deed between Thomas Blincoe and Hardage Lane (1778).
    Deed between Amiah Bonham and George Shively (1791).
    Deed between Nicholas Borders and John Backer (1794).
    Deed between William Boyles and Matthew Harrison (1796).
    Deed between George Bustle and James Greenleese (1802).
    Deed between Hugh Brent and Martin Brent (1809).
    Deed between James Burson and Aaron Burson (1811).
    Deed between James Booth and Christopher Burnhouse (1815).
    Deed between Daniel Brown and Jonas Potts (1815).
    Deed between John Brown and Levi Williams (1817).
    Deed between Benjamin Brooke and Ann Gibson (1818).
    Deed between Martin Brent and Robert J. Taylor (1819).
    Deed between Henry Brooke John Hamilton (1820).
    Deed between E.C. Brown and Burr Powell (estate of James Channel) (1821).
    Deed between Isaac Brown and John Dunkin (1825).
    Deed between.
  - Loudoun County Unrecorded Deeds Grantor C, 1757-1819. (Box 7, Folder 3, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1232)
    Deed between John Carlyle and Nicholas Minor (1757).
    Deed between Joseph Combs and Thomas Lewis (1773).
    Deed between Alexander Cooper and Joseph Stephens (1782).
    Deed between Frederick Clyne and William Gallaher (1795).
    Deed between Apollo Cooper and Matthew Rust (1795).
    Deed between John Carnell and William Mains (1797).
    Deed between Jacob Crumbacker and Phillip Filler (1797).
    Deed between Thomas Chinn and John Upp (1803).
    Deed between Adam Cordel and Anthony Conrad (1804).
    Deed between Washington Cocke and John Spencer (1809).
    Deed between William Carpenter and Phineas Thomas (1815).
    Deed between John Crupp and Daniel Johnston (1819).
  - Loudoun County Unrecorded Deeds Grantor D, 1796-1881. (Box 7, Folder 4, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1232)
    Deed between Thomas Davis and Robert Acres (1796.
    Deed between Daniel Davis and John McKinney (1808).
    Deed between Solomon Davis and Lewis Ellzey (1812).
    Deed between Alexander Darne and Thomas Newman (1881).
  - Loudoun County Unrecorded Deeds Grantor E, 1789-1860. (Box 7, Folder 5, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1232)
    Deed between William Ellzey and Robert Todd (1789).
    Deed between George Emrey and Patrick Cowan (1796).
    Deed between Thomas Ellzey and David Lacy (1799).
    Deed between Casper Echart and John Hough (c. 1800).
    Deed between George Emrey and Peter Boss (1804).
    Deed between William Ellzey and Lewis Ellzey (1805).
    Deed between Lewis Ellzey amd Davod Lovett (1810).
    Deed between Charles Evard and Matthew Harrison (1860).
  - Loudoun County Unrecorded Deeds Grantor F, 1785-1822. (Box 7, Folder 6, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1232)
    Deed between Jacob Firestone and Rachel Roach (1785).
    Deed between Agnes France and Jacob Shoemaker (1787).
    Deed between Alexander Frazier and James Beatty (1794).
    Deed between John Fitzgerald estate and Joseph Vandeventer (1800).
    Deed between John Fitzgerald estate and Samuel Murray (1800).
    Deed between John Fitzgerald estate and John Hamilton (1800).
    Deed between Gabriel Fox and Amos Fox (1794).
    Deed between Philip Frome and Michael Ruse (1800).
    Deed between Ferdinand Fairfax and James McIlhaney (1803).
    Deed between Ferdinand Fairfax and James Coleman (1803).
    Deed between Hannah Fearst and Thomas Hough (1805).
    Deed between Jacob Fawley and John Slater (1809).
    Deed between Josiah Fulkerson and Nortam Urton (1811).
    Deed between Minor Firr and William Newton (1811).
    Deed between Amos Fox and Daniel Fox (1812).
    Deed between Caleb Fox and Daniel Fox (1812).
    Deed between Amos Ferguson and William Noland (1812).
    Deed between Joseph Fox and Daniel Fox (1813).
    Deed between George Finch and John Campbell (1815).
    Deed between Isaac Fry and Jacob Silcott (1822).
  - Loudoun County Unrecorded Deeds Grantor G, 1761-1829. (Box 7, Folder 7, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1232)
    Deed between John Gladin and Robert Adam (1761).
    Deed between George Gragg and John Walton (1768).
    Deed between Enoch Grigsby and James Land (1769).
    Deed between John Griffith and William Jones (1771).
    Deed between Henry Gunnell and Josiah Clapham (1793).
    Deed between Elizabeth Graham and Richard Weeden (1795).
    Deed between George Gregg and Joseph Janney executors (1798).
    Deed between Mark Gore and Edward Dowlin (1810).
    Deed between William Gregg and Thomas Gregg (1812).
    Deed between William Graham and William Bromough (1814).
    Deed between Joseph Garrett and David Beall (1815).
    Deed between Benjamin Grayson and George Rust (1816).
    Deed between Alice Gibson and Samuel Peach (1820).
    Deed between James Gilmore and Joseph Newton (1827).
    Deed between John Gray and George W. Henry (1829).
  - Loudoun County Unrecorded Deeds Grantor H, 1770-1823. (Box 7, Folder 8, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1232)
    Deed between John Hough and Francis Keen (1770).
    Deed between John Hough and John Sutton (1789).
    Deed between James Hamilton and John Mathias (1791).
    Deed between William Hough and Jacob Wine (1801).
    Deed between John Harrison and Sampson Guy (1804).
    Deed between James Hixson and Matthew Rust etc. (1806).
    Deed between Andrew Hospital and George Henry (1823).
  - Loudoun County Unrecorded Deeds Grantor J, 1778-1780. (Box 7, Folder 9, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1232)
    Deed between William and John Johnston and William Lane (1778).
    Deed between Leven Powell and George Johnston and John Heryford (1780).
  - Loudoun County Unrecorded Deeds Grantor L, 1779-1837. (Box 7, Folder 10, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1232)
    Deed between Septimus Levering and Patrick Cavan (1779).
    Deed between Joseph Lewis and Ben Powell (1797).
    Deed between Thomas Lewis and Leven Luckett (1797).
    Deed between Thomas Ludwell Lee and James Revell (1805).
    Deed between Richard Bland Lee and Stephen Donaldson (1805).
    Deed between Joanna Lewis and Martin Brent (1819).
    Deed between David Lovett and John Jones (1837).
  - Loudoun County Unrecorded Deeds Grantor M, 1761-1812. (Box 7, Folder 11, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1232)
    Deed between George Mercer and Edward Dolan (1763).
    Deed between Harrison Manley and John Thornton (1772).
    Deed between Stephen T. Mason and Adam Eckart (1790).
    Deed between Nathaniel Moss and Baptist Church at Goose Creek (1793).
    Deed between Abraham Mason and John Mason (1805, 1812).
  - Loudoun County Unrecorded Deeds Grantor N, 1759, 1801. (Box 7, Folder 12, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1232)
    Deed between Willoughby Newton and William Jett (1759).
    Deed between John Norris and Thomas Stones (1801).
  - Loudoun County Unrecorded Deeds Grantor O, 1796-1822. (Box 7, Folder 13, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1232)
    Deed between Alexander D. Orrs and Susannah Orr (1796).
    Deed between Joel Oxley and Henry Oxley Jr. (1796).
    Deed between Overseers of the Poor and T. H. Peyton (1803).
    Deed between Overseers of the Poor and James Donough (1815).
    Deed between Overseers of the Poor and Thomas Flowers (1815).
    Deed between Overseers of the Poor and William Wright (1815).
    Deed between Overseers of the Poor and Fielding Brown (1815).
    Deed between Overseers of the Poor and Charles Binns (1815).
    Deed between Overseers of the Poor and Charles Binns, William Wright, Fielding Brown, Thomas Flowers, and James Donough (1816).
    Deed between William G. Orr and Thomson Mason (1822).
  - Loudoun County Unrecorded Deeds Grantor P, 1761-1888. (Box 7, Folder 14, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1232)
    Deed between Thomas Phillips and Alexander Arnold (1761).
    Deed between Benjamin Payne and Francis Adams etc. (1788).
    Deed between Evan Phillips and Samuel Dixson (1792).
    Deed between John Price and William Wright (1799).